WILD MECHANICS
SCARFACE | JAGUAR VS CAIMAN
THE AMBUSH
THE TANGLED EDGE OF A BRAZILIAN RIVER, A HUNTER STALKS THE SHADOWS.
IS A JAGUAR,
A MALE IN HIS PRIME.
SCARFACE
WHO KNOW HIM, CALL HIM SCARFACE.
FROM A WOUND HE EARNED CLAWING HIS WAY TO SUPREMACY.
MONSTERS
HIS TERRITORY CRAWLS WITH MONSTERS.
COUSINS OF THE CROCODILE ARE WAITING TO GRAB ALMOST ANYTHING THAT COMES NEAR THE WATER.
THEY FEAR HIM
BUT ITS SCARFACE THEY FEAR.
BECAUSE WHERE THE LAND ENDS,
HIS HUNTING GROUND BEGINS.
THE STRIKE
APEX PREDATOR
IS THE TOP PREDATOR IN A LAND OF PREDATORS, THE BEST OF THE BEST.
CAIMAN KILL
EVERY MEAL
BUT EVERY MEAL IS A BATTLE.
King of the Pantanal